Now,what about the computers?
现在，电脑怎么样？
I think it might be a good idea to install some new models.
我想装一些新型号是一个好主意。
They would take up a lot less room and so that would increase the work space for text books and so on.
它们占用的空间少，这样可以增加参考书等资源的运行空间。
That would be great.It is a bit cramped in there at times.
太好了。有时里面的地方是很小。
What about other resources?
其他资源怎么样？
Do you have a list of things that the students would like to see improved?
你有学生们希望改进的单子目录吗？
Yes,one of the comments that students frequently make is that they find it difficult to find materials that are appropriate for their level,
是的。学生们经常说难以找到适合自己水平的材料，
especially reading resources,so I think we need to label them more clearly.
特别是读书资源，所以我想我们需要把它们标记得更清楚一些。
Well that's easy enough,we can get that organised very quickly.
这很简单，我们可以很快弄好。
In fact I think we should review all of the study resources as some of them are looking a bit out-of-date.
事实上，我觉得我们应该检查一下所有的学习资源，因为有些资源已经有点过时了。
Definitely.The CD section especially needs to be more current.
当然。特别是光盘区需要更新。
I think we should get some of the ones that go with our latest course books and also make multiple copies.
我认为我们应该引进一些与最新课本配套的资源，并且多留一些副本。